(Raj:)That's funny because those aren't the
kind of kisses you want on your nipples.
- What is that?
- This is a list...
(Sheldon:)...of your heinous acts
against Leonard...
(Sheldon:)...one of which is certainly the cause of
him wetting his bed well into his teens.
Fourteen is not...
Uh, yeah, never mind.
(Jimmy:)What's this word?
(Leonard:)Nancy.
(Leonard:)You called me Nancy
for three years.
(Sheldon:)You really need to work
on your penmanship.
(Jimmy:)Man, I...
(Jimmy:)I don't know what to say.
(Sheldon:)I thought
we were just having some fun.
Well, it wasn't fun for me.
(Sheldon:)You're being too kind, Leonard.
You ruined him.
(Leonard:)Come on, guys.
- That was pretty bad-ass, dude.
- I help the weak.